

### **Profile**

Full-Stack Development Expert here!.

My top skill is MEANStack, MERNStack(express,node,MongoDB,angular,react). My skills are Angular,Vue,Next.js,HTML5,bootstrap,sass, scss, css

I'm honest and sincere developer.

I have + 9 years of experience at web development.

I have already implemented lots of projects like Multi-vendor E-commerce site, wedding site, educational site and so on.

So if you hire me, I can complete this project in a short time as you want. I am available for now and I can start working right now. I guarantee the best quality of my working. I'd like to discuss more in detail via chat.

Best regards.

# **Employment History**

Web Developer and Design (Full-stack developer & TeamLead), SHEN YANG XI HAO SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY LTD COMPANY, Shenyang

DECEMBER 2015 - APRIL 2019

- · Hired, trained and supervised a team of 3 project managers.
- · Presented drawings to project managers and incorporated recommended changes.

### Full Stack Developer, IT Computer Solutions, ShenYang

JANUARY 2013 - MARCH 2015

- · Reviewed project goals and objectives with the project manager and design team.
- · Implemented projects like e-commerce, exam site by yourself using MERN,MEAN stack

## Education

Master of Computer Applications - MCA, Tsinghua University, Beijing

APRIL 2009 - MARCH 2013

#### My Past Working

APRIL 2013 - PRESENT

- Living Urls
- https://mercologo.com/
- https://www.nugget.ai/
- https://www.shaadisaga.com/
- · printandframeit.com
- · https://www.litmus.com/
- https://www.khanacademy.org/
- http://blog.shoedazzle.com/

#### **Details**

WenAnRu TongDaXinCun 3-5-2, Shenyang, China 13002491670 fujingforward@gmail.com

NATIONALITY

Chinese

07/27/1992

#### Links

Linkedin

Github

#### Skills

Angular

React

Node.js

Codeigniter

Laravel

Vue

Python

ASP.NET

React-Native

## Languages

English

#### **Hobbies**

Football, Reading, Watching, ...

- Heorku Working Urls
- http://wedeye.herokuapp.com/
- http://stock-market-good.herokuapp.com/
- http://movieplayer.herokuapp.com/
- http://morning-ocean-93521.herokuapp.com
- App Store
- https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.view9.foreveryng